madsubmitter.com 2016-10-29

# Submit Your Website URL Free - MadSubmitter Privacy policy

##  MadSubmitter Privacy Policy

Privacy Policy:

MadSubmitter.com respects the privacy of its users. The policies below are in effect on the whole MadSubmitter.com property: website and newsletter.

No Spam  
MadSubmitter.com does not practice or tolerate spam in any shape or form. We may occasionally communicate your email address or contact information to a MS partners, this will only be done if the service or product being offered is directly beneficial to the MS user. Alternate third-party organizations will never receive this information unless a) you explicitly elect to do so by joining MadSubmitter services, or by) MS or its assets are acquired one day. Due to the nature of the Search Engine Submission service, MadSubmitter.com submits your site and contact information to some search engines. 

Data Collection  
The following data is collected and stored in our database when you use an MadSubmitter.com service: email, name, address, phone, site url, site name and description. We you select; our free website submission, premium website submission, directory submission & search engines optimization your personal information & website data will be also stored in our database. This data is only collected for the personalized used of these services. 

Cookies  
MadSubmitter.com uses cookies for some of its services (e.g. Site Submission). The sole purpose of these cookies is to provide better personalization of our services. We never use these cookies to track customer habits or behaviour.   

  * Google ads on this site:  
Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on our site. 
  * Google's use of the DART cookie enables it and its partners to serve ads to our users based on their visit to our site and/or other sites on the Internet. 
  * Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad & content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html). 

Opt-In  
All members of the MadSubmitter.com Newsletter have given MadSubmitter.com their permission to be added to the list. At each signup MadSubmitter.com collects the IP address of the new member's computer and signup time. This is only used to identify malicious people that sign up with someone else's email address.

Opt-Out  
If, at any time, you whish to be removed from the MadSubmitter Newsletter, you can follow the removal instructions included in each published issue.
